这是我们的用户创建函数,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: There's
our user creator function,
注意不要在里面创建一个物体。
notice no creating an object inside of it.
不与某些共享存储或函数建立联系，也不返回对象。
No making a bond to some shared store or
functions, no returning an object out.
因为我们要借助新的,
Because we're gonna run that
function with the help of the new,
我们可以称之为修饰语。
we can call that a modifier.
它改变了用户创建者执行上下文的行为,
It alters the behavior of the user
creator execution context,
当我们运行它的时候，它会自动为我们插入东西。
it's gonna insert stuff in there
automatically for us when we run it.
但是等一下，我们需要一个共享的功能存储，一个是铜的。
But hold on, we need a shared store
of functions one, copper one.
你觉得怎么样，这些函数的一个保存版本。
What do you say,
one save version of those functions.
我们怎么确保和他们有联系？
How are we gonna make sure
we have a bond to them?
原来用户创建函数也是一个对象,
Well, it turns out that user
creator function is also an object,
函数对象组合。
function object combo.
这就是函数，我们只是不讨论对象，但大多数时候。
That's what a function is, we just don't
talk about the object but most the time.
它的对象位有一个叫做 prototype into 的属性
And its object bit has
a property called prototype into
我们要存储和增量方法。
which we're going to store and
increment method.
让我们通过人群，这里我们一行一行地来看民谣。
Let's go through people,
here we go folk line by line.
杰夫，如果你不介意把它拿走的话，实际上是完整的
Jeff, if you don't mind taking it away
actually with a full kind of complete
称为全局存储器。
description as global memory.
杰夫，在第一行完整地描述我们在做什么
Jeff, complete description of what
we're doing in that very first line
不仅仅是声明一个函数，对吗？
more than just declaring a function,
right?
我们在做什么？
What are we doing?
演讲者2: 我们正在创建一个名为用户创造者的标签。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: We're creating
a label called user creator.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 太棒了，这是一个函数定义，但是
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Fantastic,
it's a function definition stored it, but
还有什么？
what else?
说话人2: 这隐含了一个对象。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: That
implicitly has an object.
威尔 · 森特斯: 我不介意这里隐含的意思，是的,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: I don't mind
the word implicit there, yeah,
它是一个函数对象组合，我喜欢这样称呼它。
it has it is a function object combo,
as I like to call it.
它有一个函数声明，或者函数定义,
There it is, it has both a function
declaration, or function definition sorry,
这是一个函数和一个物体的组合。
that is the combination of
a function plus an object.
这就是我们在定义函数时所做的。
That is what we're doing when
we're defining a function.
我们只是大部分时间不谈论这件事，但它总是存在的。
We just don't talk about this thing most
of the time, but it's there, always.
好了，现在，我们还没有完全结束。
Okay, now, we're not still quite done yet.
亚当，这个物体不是空的。
Adam, this object is not an empty object.
它是一个物体，上面有什么属性？
It's an object with, what property on it?
什么问题是如何自动走向的？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: What problem
is it how automatically towards?
亚当: 原型 威尔 · 森塔斯: 原型，亚当,
&gt;&gt; Adam: Prototype.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Prototype, and Adam,
这么大的一个古董，里面装的是什么？
what is that prototype property
got stored in it a big old?
亚当: 空物体。
&gt;&gt; Adam: Empty object.
Will Sentance: 空的物体，所以
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Empty object, so
这就是我们在函数定义中所做的。
this is literally what we're doing
in just our function definition.
我们只是不经常谈到这一点，但是
We just don't talk about this
bit of it that often but
就在那儿，函数，对象组合。
it's there, function, object combo.
这个物体有一个叫做原型的属性，这个属性本身就是一个很大的古老物体
And that object's got a property called
prototype which is itself a big old object
储存在里面。
stored on it.
我怎样才能到达这个物体？
How do I get to this object?
丹，我要写什么样的文字才能写出这里的东西？
Dan, what's my kind of words do I
write to get to the object here?
创造者，原型。
&gt;&gt; Dan: Creator.prototype.
Will Sentance: Usercreated.prototype，这将给我这个对象。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Usercreated.prototype,
and that's going to give me the object.
如果我想在那个物体里存储一些东西，丹，我会写什么？
If I wanted to store something in
that object Dan, what would I write?
Usercreator-Dan: . prototype.-
Usercreator-
&gt;&gt; Dan: .prototype.-
威尔 · 森塔斯: 随便什么标签
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Whatever the label would
就是为了这个。
be for that that exactly.
恐怕我们得走了。
I'm afraid there we go.
我们开始吧，丹，我们在这里做什么
Here we go on that note,
Dan, what are we doing here
因为我们要使用这个对象，就像函数存储的用途一样
because we're gonna use this object
like how use a function store was for
每个函数的一个垂直保存版本。
a single vert save
version of each function.
我们希望任何运行后返回的对象
That we want any objects that
get returned from running
用户创建器访问任何存储的函数在这里。
user creator to have access
to any stored function here.
丹，我们要把教给我的东西一个字一个字地储存起来,
And Dan, what are we gonna store taught
me through word by word by word,
从左到右。
the left to the right.
我们正在寻找用户创建者。
&gt;&gt; Dan: We're looking for user creator.
我们要去原型机那里。
We're going to the prototype.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 嗯，我不会使用原型，但是
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Well,
I wouldn't use a prototype but
听起来很神奇。
it sounds like something magical.
Dan: 我们将进入-Will Sentance: User creates object
&gt;&gt; Dan: We're going to the-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: User creates object
自身的版本，我们要找的自身的对象部分，上面有什么属性？
version of itself, object part of itself
which we look for, what property on it?
丹: 原型-威尔 · 森塔斯: 当然,
&gt;&gt; Dan: Prototype-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Absolutely,
我们找到了一个？
which we find is a?
丹: 空物体威尔 · 森塔斯: 谢天谢地,
&gt;&gt; Dan: Empty object
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Thank goodness,
因为我们接下来要做什么，我们要做什么？
because what we try and
do next, we try to?
创建一个新的标签增量。
&gt;&gt; Dan: Create a new label increment.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 太棒了，在那个物体里
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Fantastic,
in that object-
阿丹: 还要存储一个函数。
&gt;&gt; Dan: And store a function.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 老实说，我知道为了在年做这个
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: I honestly got to
say I know in order to do this in
这样的录音版本，但这值得一阵掌声。
this sort of recorded version, but
that deserves a round of applause.
谢谢你 Dan 你真是太好了。
Thank you, Dan.
That was very, very nice.
(掌声)威尔 · 森坦斯: 丹说得好。
&gt;&gt; [APPLAUSE]
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Nice from Dan.
我们让伊森在这里做下一个。
Let's have Ethan do the next one here.
在查用户创建者 Ethan？
So looking up user creator, Ethan?
伊森: 是的。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: Yes.
威尔 · 森特斯: 发现它是一个函数加一个对象,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Finding that
it's a function plus an object,
我们要在这里访问它的函数位，还是它的对象位？
are we gonna access its function bit here,
or its object bit here?
伊森: 反对。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: Object.
Will Sentance: Object bit，使用点符号，和
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Object bit,
using dot notation, and
它有一个属性的对象叫什么？
it's got a property on the object called?
原型 威尔 · 森塔斯: 它本身就是,
&gt;&gt; Ethan: Prototype.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Which is itself,
感谢上帝，一个物体，因为我们要尝试
thank goodness, an object,
because we're gonna try and
用那个原型物体做什么。
do what with that prototype object.
我们要试着分配它吗？
We're gonna try and assign it?
伊森: 还有标签登录。
&gt;&gt; Ethan: And label login.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 太棒了，在属性登录时，给它分配一个功能,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Fantastic, at the
property login and assign it a function,
一种方法。
a method.
伙计们看看这个,
Look at that, folks, look at that,
这样的存储单一版本的功能。
that such store of single
version of our functions.
好的很好。
Okay, good.
现在移到下一行。
Now move down to the next line.
布雷登，左手边。
Braydon, left-hand side.
那句话是什么意思? 等一下，让我做我的左手边。
What's that saying?
Hold on, let me just do my left-hand side.
布莱登，该怎么办？
Braden, what to say to do?
Braydon: 不要声明一个常量用户为1。
&gt;&gt; Braydon: Don't declare
a constant user one.
Will Sentance: 声明一个常量用户为。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Declare
a constant user one.
我们知道里面放什么吗，布雷顿？
Do we know what to store in it, Braydon?
布雷登: 不仅仅是——威尔 · 森坦斯: 我们不知道。
&gt;&gt; Braydon: Not just-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We have no idea.
千万不要看那个新的关键词
Do not ever look at that new key word and
认为用户一这是一个不同的功能。
think somehow user one this
is a different to a function.
我们在右手边做什么，布雷登？
What are we doing on the right-hand
side there, Brayden?
暂时保持新鲜，你在右手边做了什么？
Hold the new for now,
what did you do in right-hand side?
布雷顿: 你在给用户创建者打电话
&gt;&gt; Braydon: You're
calling the user creator
威尔 · 森特斯: 我们在打电话,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: We're calling,
我们正在执行，我们正在使用 Prince 运行用户创建函数。
we're executing, we're running
the user create function with Prince.
没有什么魔法，没有什么不同，没有什么东西,
Nothing magic, nothing different,
nothing object,
就叫做用户创造者。
is just literally call user creator.
前面有一个特殊的三个字母的单词，可以做很多事情
With a special three-letter word in
front that's gonna do a ton of stuff
在用户创建器的执行上下文中。
inside user creator's execution context.
好吧，那么现在，我们的用户1是 Brayden？
All right, so for now,
our user1 is, Brayden?
未初始化。
&gt;&gt; Braydon: Uninitialized.
威尔 · 森特斯: 没有初始化，是的，很好。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Uninitialized,
yeah, perfect.
好了我们开始吧。
All right, here we go.
这是最后一块了，最后一块，各位。
This is the final, final piece, people.
好的，用户创造者，我要用蓝色来做我的新东西。
Okay, user creator, I'm gonna use blue for
my stuff that new does.
这就是我们的新号召,
So there's our new, calling,
和往常一样，调用函数。
just as usual, calling the function.
只要稍微改变一下,
Just with a slight little change,
在执行过程中会发生什么。
in terms of what it's gonna do
inside the execution context.
在执行过程中会自动化大量的事情。
It's gonna automate a ton of stuff
inside that execution context.
与 Eva 和9一起呼叫 userCreator。
Calling userCreator with Eva, and 9.
我想这几乎是我们最后的机会了。
I think it's almost our
last chance to do this.
它是一个品牌，它是一个全新的？
It's a brand, it's a brand new?
演讲者2: 执行情境。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Execution context.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 执行环境，听起来很神奇。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Execution context,
it sounds amazing.
这就是了，这是一个大问题。
There it is, it's a huge one.
就是这样，我仍然，总有一天我会做得很好。
There it is, I still,
one day I'll get good at that.
这就是巨大的执行环境。
There it is, huge execution context.
直觉，你去，是的，直觉，我们去,
Intuit you go, yep, Intuit we go,
还有，威尔 · 森特斯: 在我们当地,
and,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: In our local,
威尔 · 句子: 记忆。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Memory.
首先，让我们处理参数参数组合。
First, let's handle our
parameter argument combinations.
彼得，这个函数的输入是什么？
Peter, our,
inputs to this function, are what?
彼得: 伊娃-威尔 · 森坦斯: 我们先做那个吧。
&gt;&gt; Peter: Eva-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Let's do that one first.
它被分配给函数中的哪个参数，哪个占位符？
Eva, and it's assigned to what parameter,
what placeholder inside the function?
彼得: 姓名 威尔 · 森坦斯: 名字，完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Peter: Name.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Name, exactly.
不要认为这些是对象或者属性,
Don't think these are objects,
or properties, or by the way,
任何与新的关键字，这是正则输入的函数。
anything to do with new keyword that
is regular inputs for function.
下一个，又是彼得？
The next one, Peter again?
彼得: 得分是9分。
&gt;&gt; Peter: Score is 9.
Will Sentance: 是的，score 参数是值9的参数。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah, score parameter
is the argument of the value 9.
这就像我们在这个函数中声明变量一样。
That is like if we declare
the variables inside this function.
我们可以在这里面写，我不知道，名字也行。
We could just write inside here,
I don't know, const name is either.
但是我们不想让它变得如此非一般，如此不灵活。
But we don't wanna make it so
non-general, [LAUGH] so inflexible.
我们希望每次运行这个函数的时候都能改变它，好吗？
We wanna be able to have it change
each time we run this function, okay?
那就是，白色笔下，蓝色笔下的时间。
That's, white pen down, blue pen time.
这个函数的意义在于，无论我们在这里做什么，都是为了创造,
The whole point of this function, whatever
we're doing here is to create what,
布雷顿？
Braydon?
布雷顿: 一个物体。
&gt;&gt; Braydon: An object.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 一个客体。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: An object.
我们是否需要在每次执行函数时手动声明一个对象
Do we wanna have to manually declare
an object every time you do a function
是这样吗？
that does this?
没有，那我们的新关键词是什么？
No, so what's our new key words?
它要做的第一件事是什么，布雷顿？
First thing it's gonna do, Braydon?
Braydon: 分配空对象。
&gt;&gt; Braydon: Assign empty object.
是的，声明并保存在内存中。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah,
declare and save in memory.
一个空的物体。
An empty object.
我们希望能够得到访问，这样我们就可以把东西放进去。
We wanna be able to get access so
we can stick stuff into it.
我们给它贴的标签是什么，布雷顿？
What is the label we've
given to access it, Braydon?
布雷顿: 这个 威尔 · 森塔斯: 这真是太美了,
&gt;&gt; Braydon: This.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: This, exactly beautiful,
设置为空对象。
set this to empty object.
Beaituful.
好吧。
All right.
但是当它最终返回到用户一时，我们不会反对
But we will not object when it eventually
gets returned out into user one
访问我们的单一保存版本的功能。
to have access to our single
save version of the functions.
我们希望它能记住我们的整个目标。
We want it to have access to remember,
our whole goal here.
所以我可以用一点点增量来做到这一点。
So I can do this using
one little increments.
这是整个工作坊的唯一目标。
That's the only goal
of the whole workshop.
图标是否具有适用于该用户的功能,
Is the icon have the functionality
that applies to that user one,
不是所有的10万行代码，但是
not all over the whole
100,000 lines of code, but
取而代之的是，在我们的用户上有一个对象。
instead, right there on
our user one object.
排行榜上所有的测验问题都不分享，没有。
Not being shared by all the quiz
questions in the league tables, no.
就在这里，在我们的 user1对象上，这是我们唯一的目标。
Right there, on our user1 object,
it's our only goal.
但是要知道我们不能把增量函数直接存储在对象上,
But know we can't have increment
function directly stored on that object,
我们想要的是一个链接，通过其原始参考。
we wanna have instead a link
through its proto reference to.
Will Sentance: 这个共享的函数存储。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: this
shared store of functions.
那么 Braydon，你认为他们隐藏的原始财产会链接到什么呢？
And so Braydon, what do you think their
hidden proto property is going to link to?
具体点，具体在哪里？
Be very specific, exactly where?
布雷顿: 它将连接到
&gt;&gt; Braydon: It's going to
link to the object part of
原型属性的用户创建器函数。
the user creator function
to the prototype property.
威尔 · 森塔斯: 哪个是它本身？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Which is itself?
布雷顿: 一个物体。
&gt;&gt; Braydon: An object.
威尔 · 森坦斯: 一个对象，充满了我们放在里面的功能。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: An object, full of
the functions that we've put in there.
非常，非常，非常好，非常感谢布雷登。
Very, very, very nice there,
much appreciated by Braydon.
从布雷登到那个东西，简直太棒了。
From Brayden there,
up to that object, fantastic.
好了，现在我们回到正题。
Okay, now we're back to us.
这是它做的第二件事，设置运行的函数的原型,
So that's the second thing it does, set
proto to the function that's being run,
对象版本的原型属性，它本身就是一个对象。
onto its prototype property of its object
version, which is itself an object.
因此我们将原型设置为 userCreate，或者
So we set the proto to userCreate, or
不管功能是什么，这已经成为了新的关键词，原型。
whatever the function is, this has been
rather the new keyword .prototype.
这些都是通过我们的新关键字自动生成的。
This is all automated by
the new keyword for us.
这看起来已经很不错了，不是吗？
This is looking pretty nice already,
right?
但是现在我们必须得到一些实际的具体数据。
But now we've got to get some
actual specific data in.
丹，对你来说，丹: 我们运行这一行的栈名称,
Dan, to you
&gt;&gt; Dan: We run the line the stack name,
威尔 · 森塔斯: 太棒了。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Fantastic.
我们把这个加到本地存储器里，威尔 · 森坦斯: 是的。
&gt;&gt; Dan: We add this in the local memory,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yeah.
丹: 并创建一个新的标签名称标志的名称-
&gt;&gt; Dan: And creates a new label
name signs that the name-
威尔 · 森塔斯: 我想说,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: I would say here,
因为我们不想搞混
because we don't wanna get confused
和我们的丹: 是的。
with our
&gt;&gt; Dan: Yeah.
Will Sentance: 变量名或参数、新的属性名和
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Variable names or
parameters, a new property name and
被我无情地选中了那会是工作吗 Dan？
very unhelpfully chosen by me,
which is gonna be work, Dan?
阿丹: 年通过的那个论点。
&gt;&gt; Dan: The argument that was passed in.
哪一个是？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Which is?
太棒了。
Fantastic.
顺便说一下，丹，你的技术社区非常出色。
By the way, Dan your technical
community is outstanding.
那下一行呢？
And then the next line?
阿丹: 同样的事情，但在这方面的分数-威尔森坦斯: 自动创建
&gt;&gt; Dan: Same thing but with score on this-
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: The auto-created
新关键字的帮助下创建一个对象，它有标签？
object with the help of the new keyword,
which has got the label?
丹: 这个 威尔 · 森塔斯: 这个，没错，还有
&gt;&gt; Dan: This.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: This, exactly, and
我们去找它，然后我们发现，它有什么特性吗？
we go to it and we find,
does it have a score property?
丹: 没有 威尔 · 森塔斯: 不，是这样
&gt;&gt; Dan: No.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: No, so
我们成功了，就是这样。
we make it, there it is.
我们分配到这个任务，什么，丹？
And we assigned to it, what, Dan?
丹: 9 威尔 · 森塔斯: 我们学校的价值
&gt;&gt; Dan: 9.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: The value of our school
参数是策略的参数，也就是9。
parameter which is the argument that
was policy which is 9, exactly.
那是一个相当不错的民间，那正是我们想要的。
Folk that is a pretty nice,
that's exactly what we want.
但是它被限制在我们的用户创造者内部的一个函数中,
But it's stuck inside a function,
inside of our user creator,
我正在查看用户创建器，我没有看到任何返回。
and I'm looking at user creator I
don't see anything returned out.
什么标志，你认为我们的新关键字自动化是最后一件事吗？
What Mark, do you think is the last
thing that our new keyword automates?
阿丹: 还这个。
&gt;&gt; Dan: Returning the this.
威尔 · 森特斯: 记住，把这个还回去，完全正确。
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Remember that,
returning this, exactly right.
返回分配给这个关键字的对象,
Returning the object assigned to this,
keyword,
我也喜欢蓝色的，对吧？
I like to do it in blue as well, right?
因为它是自动的，返回到全局标签。
Because it's automatic,
returning it out into the global label.
这里的整个部分计算转换为返回的对象，并且
This whole portion here evaluates
turns into the returned object, and
储存在哪里？
stored into what?
1 with name,
Into user1 with name,
有趣的是我现在已经改变了
it's funny that I've now changed
这个颜色，没什么用。
the color, is not helpful.
好了，亲爱的，是的,
There we go, well, dear, yeah,
用我们隐藏的原始财产原型
with our hidden proto property__proto
下划线是到 userCreator.product 的链接
underscore which is a link
up to userCreator.product
这个用于共享功能的大对象。
this big object for the shared functions.
好，现在执行上下文在这里，停留还是去？
Okay, now execution context here,
stays or goes?
完全正确，突然挂断了电话。
Goes, exactly, popped off the call stat.
我们没有显示这个呼叫，但是它被删除了
We didn't show the call stat,
but it's deleted, and
现在我们要做最重要的检查。
now we do our all important check.
一直以来我们唯一在乎的。
The only thing we really
cared about the whole time.
如果我可以做 user1.increment。
If can I do user1.increment.
顺便说一句，这就是为什么我要告诉你们解决方案二，做到了。
And by the way people, this is why I'd
tell you solution two, did the job.
解决方案三就是让我们的大部分工作自动化，这太棒了。
Solution three is just automating so much
of that job for us, which is fantastic.
但是在引擎盖下面，它是完全相同的，在做完全相同的事情方面。
But under the hood, it's exactly the same,
in terms of doing exactly the same stuff.
是的，它必须做一些小小的改变。
Yes, it has to make a few little changes.
我们必须把我们所有的函数放在这个对象中，因为我们不能控制它。
We have to put all our functions in this
object, cuz we don't get it controlled.
所以我们最好把它放在 JavaScript 知道它们会出现的地方。
So we better put it somewhere where
JavaScript knows they're gonna be.
我们把这个作为对象的标签。
We've got this as the label for
the object.
但除此之外，一切都是一样的。
But otherwise, it's exactly the same.
另外，我们可以做这一件事。
Also, we can do this one thing.
将我们的函数和数据捆绑在一起，以便于进行推理，但是
Have our functions and data bundle
together for our ease of reasoning, but
我们不能在物体上实现这些功能。
we can't have the functions
literally on the object.
否则，我已经复制了每一个用户对象，用户1，用户2,
Otherwise, I've been copied on every
single user object, user one, user two,
用户500。
user 500.
我们浪费了记忆空间。
We waste memory space.
所以取而代之的是，我们将它们保存在一个单独的版本中。
So instead, we have them in
one place single save version.
而 Java 原型的原型特性将包含 JavaScript。
And the proto feature of Java
prototype will feature JavaScript.
所有对象都有一个原始属性。
It's proto property that
all objects have a.
我们将其设置为链接到该对象，因为我们知道当 JavaScript
We set it to link up to that object,
knowing that when JavaScript
运行 user1.increment，它是否能很好地执行，让我们看看。
runs user1.increment, and
does it fight well, let's see.
托德，轮到你了。
Todd, it's your moment.
用户1我们在哪里寻找它？
User1 where do we look for it?
托德: 全球记忆。
&gt;&gt; Todd: Global memory.
威尔 · 森特斯: 全局记忆，它在那里吗？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Global memory,
is it there?
托德: 是的 是的，它是，增量。
&gt;&gt; Todd: Yes.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Yes, it is, increment.
我们看着，你告诉我？
We look on, well, you tell me?
托德: 不在那里。
&gt;&gt; Todd: Not there.
威尔 · 森塔斯: [笑]好-托德: [笑]
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: [LAUGH] Good-
&gt;&gt; Todd: [LAUGH]
对一个对象排队,
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Queue one object,
不是那里，我们会恐慌吗？
not there.
Do we panic?
托德: 没有 威尔 · 森坦斯: JavaScript 是做什么的
&gt;&gt; Todd: No.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: What does JavaScript do
自动？
automatically?
托德: 它需要原型，它会跟着用户创建者
&gt;&gt; Todd: It'll take the proto,
it'll follow that up to the user creator
对象，以及该对象中的原型属性，然后看这里。
object, and the prototype property
in that object, and look in there.
威尔 · 森特斯: 绝对出色，并找到了吗？
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Absolutely outstanding,
and find?
托德: 增量 增量，和
&gt;&gt; Todd: Increment.
&gt;&gt; Will Sentance: Increment, and
然后我们用这段代码，构建一个执行上下文。
then we take that code, and
we build an execution context.
太棒了，让我们给托德一点掌声，托德非常友好。
Amazing, let's give Todd a hand,
very nice from Todd.
这对我来说是最难的部分。
That for me is the hardest bit.
好极了，伙计们。
Excellent, people.
就是这样，一个新的关键字出售了至少一些我们的输入太多的问题,
That's it, a new keyword has sold at least
some of our typing too much problem,
但是我的天啊,
but my goodness,